Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
I am Professor of Ancient History
Dr.Benjamin Price.
Record Number Four.
The legendary "Necronomicon". "The Dead
"Book" is not just a legend.
The circle of sages found him.
Despite all my warnings. the book
They read those ominous texts...
and as evil as if Satan
himself were here.
possessing the body
They released the demons.
God help us.
Record Number Five;
We found something.
Could send them back to hell An
object of such tremendous power.
If they came back. I hid it
behind spells and talismans.
It should stay this way
because if the seal is
broken. they will feel it.
They feel its smell in the soil.
and they smell it in the air.
Then there is nothing
more than destroying it.
cannot prevent them.
I swear! He jumped out of the
window and ran towards the street.
With her panties on. just
like like in a fucking movie.
Oh my God. Don't say
Emma is calling. Don't answer.
- What if it's an emergency?
- Leo. it's not urgent.
He's going crazy that we came here.
Leave the phone in the car next time.
Stop nagging.
Let's get out of here.
- Are you kidding me?
- Don't answer that.
Don't answer your fucking phone.
Leo! If you open it. I'll leave here.
- Stop. son!
- Hello sweetie.
- Damn it...
- I was just about to call you.
Yes. we went to the lake.
Listening. correcting. translating into
Turkish and Synchronization; horizonbaba
Leo!
See you tomorrow.
I love you too.
Jared. let's fuck off!
Stop going crazy!
Jared!
Help!
What the fuck?
Jared!
Jared. where are you?
Help!
My god!
What the hell is this?
I have you. my friend.
I have you...
What's going on AQ?
- I have something for the birthday boy.
- This is very nice!
We overdid it a bit.
but you deserve it.
- It was my pleasure!
- Congratulations. buddy.
- I'll have some more champagne.
- Alice. wait.
Come here.
What was that? Are
you whistling at me?
No I just called
but you don't listen.
This is the third bottle. Maybe
we should slow down a little.
After all. today is Joseph's
birthday. We'll get a little drunk.
Okay okay! Just
good vibes. okay?
Open the gifts.
Joseph... Happy Birthday my friend.
- This is from both of us.
- There was no need. guys.
Wow.
Thanks guys.
A pen?
Not just any pen.
This is a Belvoir.
- It must have been $1000 or so.
- More. but that's not the point.
I wanted to encourage you
to finish writing your book.
Not very subtle.
This is the fifth
time it's started. so...
- “Actually. the fourth one.”
- “Fourth?”
Damn. I'm sorry. But just
look at Alice's pictures.
They were fine before but when I
got it the difference was incredible.
Sometimes all you
need is a little nudge.
Speaking of which...
- And here...
- Another one?
- Happy birthday.
- I liked the package.
- In black and white
photo everyone looks cute.
- You didn't mention this gift.
- Just something small.
- Can't compare to your Belvoir.
- Our Belvoir.
Thank you both.
You are very talented.
I always forget that you
Americans hug each other.
- Brother-in-law hug.
- Did you try to kiss my boyfriend?
You know. us French girls. hello
That being said. we like to hold hands.
Style and sophistication.
Talk about subtlety.
He's upset about my gift.
- You always complain.
- No. but cut down on your drinking.
- After all. we are celebrating.
- I know.
- But calm down AQ - Okay.
I'm done. Cigarette break?
Promise me we'll
never get married.
- Look. he didn't want to do that.
- No. of course he wanted to.
He's doing it to annoy
me. Just like with cigarettes.
We were thinking of
having a baby. but he
won't quit smoking.
This is ridiculous.
That's ridiculous.
Forget about it; You
know what he is like.
- Can I have a cigarette. boss?
- Stop it. I'm not your boss.
- I'm just sending paychecks.
- You are the boss..
- Don't you freeze in a t-shirt?
- No. it's like an oven in there.
- Also. the music is too loud.
- Yes. I keep saying it.
Are you talking nonsense
about me to my employees?
- We're just talking.
- Calm down. Mike. It's not your fault.
Alice. can you come in with me?
OK. come here.
- Don't touch me!
- Okay. relax.
Stop accusing me of things.
You are the one who did this.
You're trying to make me
sound like a hysterical drunk.
I'm sorry. okay?
Let's go.
Hey look at me -Stop
acting like a fucking child.
- Don't call me that!
- Cut that nonsense.
- Don't touch me. I said!
Damn it!
You're the one who provoked
me. I've never been like this before.
No ex-girlfriend has ever made me
this angry. What do you think this is?
If we can't talk.
How do you expect us to proceed?
Go back to Mike. you. Give him
another cigarette. Check it out at 31!
Go to hell!
Joe...
- Will. you're drunk.
- Give me the keys. Let me drop you home
Will!
AQ bitch.
Don't move.
Don't do this.
I'll call an ambulance.
I will call...
Fuck!
- Damn it.
- Will...
Will?
We found you.
Now leave us alone with your family.
What the hell is going on?
Kunda.
In Astrata.
What the hell...?
Montosse.
Help!
Canda.
Help me!
Dad. I'm here.
I have to close it.
Ok sweetie. You can
do this. You are strong.
Don't worry about his family.
Y'all You're there for Will's sake.
Of course it's scary. but
it can bring you closer.
I don't want to see them.
Thank you.
Are you taking anything
to help you sleep?
Nothing works.
- When did you come here?
- A few days ago.
Joseph lives here now. His family
gave him their summer house.
Look up.
- How long have you had a gun?
- It's not mine. Joseph's.
- I think he wants to feel punk.
- Joseph. tramp?
This is so sweet.
- Hello Polly. How are you?
- He doesn't remember you.
But after all. it's only been a year.
We must be wearing the same number.
Max. you've grown so much!
I miss you.
- Thinking about construction now...
- Don't worry. you have a break at noon.
They could probably stop at any moment.
We gathered here...
We are gathered here today to
honor the memory of William Price.
To honor him and
share his memories.
'Cause as long as these memories live
William will always be with us.
Now to his mother. Miss
Susan Price. I want to promise.
- Bonnie. what are you doing?
- No. this is Susan. grandmother.
- Aunt Bonnie passed away.
- Don't worry about him.
William.
My sweet boy.
I could talk for hours
about what a great kid he is.
A perfect young man. And a
man who makes us very proud.
He was so fond of
French cuisine that he
After completing
his education. he
brought a French
wife to his home. Alice.
Will dreamed of starting a family.
You two would make great parents.
And we could be Grandpa
Edgar and Grandma Susan
I would give anything
to be together again.
Thank you Susan. I'm really
sorry about all this turmoil.
Alice.
Do you want to share something?
Maybe a memory of your husband?
I didn't prepare a speech.
Really?
Okay... Okay.
In this case. I would like to play a
melody that means a lot to William.
Your wedding song.
I want to say goodbye
to my son for the last time.
Alright...
You can receive the
ashes within a few days.
Actually. you are
not allowed to be here.
Sir
My son just died.
Five minutes But don't tell anyone.
Thank you.
I offer my condolences.
Will!
Hold on. hold on!!
Will. I'm coming!
Will. hang on!
I am coming!
What the fuck is this?!
Come with us.
See you there.
- How far away?
- Less than five minutes.
- But what happens...
- Is everything okay?
Yeah. but you know
they don't want me there.
- This is not true.
- Here's the band-aid.
Oh my god...
They want everyone to be
together. You are part of the family.
Even my mother. He was very touched
by your acceptance of his cremation.
And he said we could
do it wherever he wanted.
- He really
appreciates you. Really.
- On the other hand. my father...
For God's sake. he can't stand you.
Oh my god...
- It looks very run down now.
- Have you been here before?
We got married here.
Mother?
Father?
I'll be right back.
Grandma. do you know
where my mother is?
He's still at school.
School ends at four.
Ok thanks.
Mother?
- What are you doing?
- What do you think?
- “After all. you invited Alice.”
- "She was Will's wife."
I will do it.
When you bought the
house. I asked you to
throw everything away.
Why are his things here?
I wanted to keep
something belonging to my
grandfather. I felt like
I was throwing it away.
- After all. he turned us down.
- I know.
But some of these
are fascinating.
Demons taking over the
body. equally evil beings...
It's like the devil himself is here.
- Do you find this fascinating?
- This is the inspiration for my book.
- Is it about your grandfather?
- No. it's not about that.
About his research.
So curses and demons...
There are all kinds of
strange devices here.
and he was a member
of a secret society.
- It was a cult.
- They were historians.
He wrote everything in his
notebook. I was going to tell you.
Let me tell you something. My
father was not a good man. Joseph.
When my mother's mind began
to wander. she stepped back.
"Circle of the Wise" He
was more important than us.
He was always going on expeditions
or burying his nose in an old book.
When my Aunt Bonnie got sick.
He completely abandoned us.
"Us Rusty Guns and Torn He abandoned his
search for the scrolls
to protect them from evil.
He was talking like this because he
couldn't face the difficulties of life!
I had to take care of this family.
I'm sorry mom.
- You should get some rest.
- No problem. Just pills.
Tell everyone lunch is in 1 hour.
Throw this away.
- Let me go!
- He insists on going out alone.
- Grandma!
- I was just trying to help.
Bonnie. I got him!
He's stealing my money!
- Call the police!
- We just...
- Grandma. how are you?
- Calm down.
- Broken.
- Wait a minute. mom.
- You thief!
- Oh my God...
Dad?
Dad.
He's out of gas.
- Don't worry about the garden.
- Someone has to do this.
I will do it but...
We gave you the house.
You left it in disrepair.
Do you want to live in this dump?
Dad...
Dad. help me...
We are inside.
Let us in. dad.
No problem.
Don't fight.
You can do.
Continue.
Do it!
Edgar?
Edgar. are you okay?
Please don't say anything to my wife...
I'll keep this. okay?
- What happened?
- I tripped in the basement. I
dropped the plates. I'm sorry.
- Yes. I heard. eat this
Can you put it on your desk?
Be careful. I did it myself.
- Really?
- This is Niobe. the Greek queen.
- Edgar's favorite.
- It's nice.
- Why did you stop doing it?
- The children came first.
Then my sister Bonnie got sick. And
my mother couldn't manage on her own.
- “You were talented. what a shame.”
- "Why should it be a pity?"
I was among the people I
loved and I built my life there.
I am nothing without my family.
Thank you Joseph.
This was nice.
Are you ok?
I'm great.
No.
That's Will's place.
Big boy Will! When
is he coming here?
Edgar. can you open the wine?
You don't do it. I'll handle it.
Ready-to-eat food;
I just warmed it up.
Joseph is right; They
are very delicious.
I wouldn't have guessed
they were frozen.
This is worrying.
It's pretty obvious
that they're dull food.
If you're going to run a
restaurant. you should be
able to tell the difference
between frozen and fresh.
Speaking of restaurants
I don't think I will...
- Let's talk about this another time.
- Let's talk about this now.
We are all here.
I haven't decided anything yet.
but it was Will's restaurant after all.
- You two did it together.
But you are his wife.
Are you sure?
Honestly for a while I had
planned to return home to Paris.
Maybe stay with my father.
You said you haven't
decided anything yet.
- We have to handle this as a family.
We have to address this as a family.
The staff loves you.
Alice. they need you.
Think about Will.
Do this for him.
Wait a minute. I know you.
You're married to my
grandson. aren't you?
Don't pretend to be
deaf. I asked a question.
- I...
- No problem.
Not only do you want to take over a
successful business. but also Will's
I'm saying he has the
opportunity to honor his memory.
This was his life's work. his passion.
- You have to move this forward
- We should talk another time.
No. it's best to put all the
cards on the table now.
- Right.
- You're driving me crazy!
- You are nothing without me!
- This is how Will wanted it to be.
- This is your damn problem!
- Do this for his sake.
We are trying to have a baby!
You don't even know what you want
Don't drive me crazy. Alice.
Alice. calm down.
I'm calm.
You shouldn't speak for Will.
I am his mother. No one
knows him better than me.
Grandma. no...
I am sad. We are
all here for his sake.
Alice is right.
It's not time.
- That's why you fail.
- Edgar. please...
Don't you dare touch me.
We are all mourning.
You don't have to be malicious.
- No problem.
- No.
Where?
Where is the wedding ring?
- Why don't you wear it?
- Did you sell it? At a good price?
- No. of course not.
- Edgar. can I have the corkscrew?
Hoodie and sneakers at
her husband's funeral...
- I'm here. Edgar. Talk to me.
- You didn't even cry.
- Isn't this weird?
- People grieve in different ways.
Get lost!
Will is dead. and now
you put us in this situation?
- That's enough. dad.
- It's your fault he died.
- You didn't stop him from driving!
- Stop it. dad!
Will got into a
fight with Alice and...
Was it my fault?
- "Of course not."
- “You couldn't stop him either.”
- This doesn't mean it's my fault.
- That's not what I meant.
- Mind your own business.
You don't know anything.
You're glad he's dead.
Please. Will is
watching us from above.
From above?
He's way down.
- Take him to the hospital!
- Thya. help me.
What did we do to deserve this?
They left without saying goodbye.
- Has he completely lost his mind?
- Thya. come on...
- He killed his dog!
- I know!
Damn. he's bleeding everywhere.
Joe. your father...
NO!
My god!
Stop it!
Let him go!
"Let it go" I said!
"Shoot. for God's sake!"
Shoot him. for God's sake!
Shoot me.
Shoot me. Joe.
Joseph!
Dating in the Cottage
Four Dead After Fire
"October 1983."
"That damn 'Book of the Dead.'
"I warned them not to read it."
"Forbidden magic.
Four words that unleash evil."
"But they didn't listen."
"December 1983.
I finally found it."
"A weapon that can stop them all."
"A dagger created by
the Circle of Sages."
"Even the slightest
wound from the ancient
sword will sever
the demons' souls."
"I hid it.
But I have to leave again."
"These creatures are hunting me and
I must protect my wife and daughters."
"Kunda."
"Astrata."
"Montosse."
Fuck it.
Alice?
- What's the problem?
- Your dog... attacked me.
I don't understand you.
What happened?
Where is your father?
I think my father killed Thya.
Open the door. it's me!
He came back for my money.
Perfect for your family.
Cheers.
Joe. it hurts. Please... Don't!
Where is your father?
We have to get out
of here. Alice. come on!
Hurry!
Edgar.
- Sweetie. Let me go!
- Mom!
You should have died. not Will.
NO!
NOT COVERED
He just stands there. staring.
- I'll be right back. mom.
Children?
Please open the door.
Have you come to give
back what you stole?
Definitely.
My god!
Mom. are you okay?
It's okay. I have you.
We will destroy them...
There are no wise men anymore...
Should I go or do
you want to go?
You go.
Take my grandmother upstairs.
Did you think that all the men
in the family would be left to you?
Joseph. come here!
- Help!
- Forget it. honey.
This isn't his style.
"Come on" I said!
Susan...
Stop spoiling the child.
He has something we need.
Give us what we came here for!
I told you he was a thief!
Have you become brave now?
Boo!
I was your first... And I'll
make sure I'm your last.
So you refused to shoot your father.
But killing me...
Is it easy?
Come here young lady! I
have what you are looking for!
I'll be right back. honey.
The money is under the bed.
Take this and leave us alone.
This place is a complete mess.
But there's something we
want inside your little head.
Your husband must
have told you where he is.
This will fix you.
Polly...
Where's your leg?
That little...
The Circle of Wise
Failed. Your grandfather
is a failure. You
will all die tonight.
Alice...
I'm coming. Alice.
Your time is up.
Joe. what is the "Circle of Wise"?
- I didn't think they were real.
- Tell me.
I saw distorted drawings.
Did Will say anything
about our grandfather?
As children. we were always
told that he was unstable.
In his diaries. he described a group
who believed that the devil was there.
And if anyone reads the
thing they'll come back...
"The Book of the Dead".
My grandfather left the
family and traveled the world to
research and collect objects
that would protect us from this.
Are they still there?
My mother wanted me to throw
everything away when she died. but...
- But what happened AQ...
- But I didn't.
There are still a few things
in the attic. And Thya...
The creature inside said they
were looking for something.
Maybe this will stop them.
Mom. drink this.
Can you look under the bed?
Your father always made sure
there were no monsters there.
- There are no monsters.
- You are lying.
Don't worry. you're safe here.
Good night mom.
Good night. Susan.
What did you say to me?
Come on honey.
Mom...
I miss you.
I miss you a lot.
We share the same
dream. It can still happen.
The whole family can be reunited.
Will is already on his
way. It will be here soon.
Don't be afraid. Susan.
Remember what you said at the funeral.
That you can give everything...
so we can all be together again.
You are nothing without your family.
I miss you.
I miss us.
You haven't kissed
me like this in years.
Your father is gone;
maybe we can...
Joseph?
Is my grandmother
okay? Is everything ok?
Yes. everything is better now.
You must trust me.
- "Trust you?"
- "They are not our enemies."
I understand this now. They just want
something back that my father stole.
I told you he was a bad man.
It's very simple. Just
tell them where you are.
Give them what they want.
and this will all be over.
We can be happy again.
What was that?
A gun.
- But we threw everything away.
- You're lying to me.
Tell us where you are.
"We"?
Where is the Kandaria dagger?
Alice. run!
Edgar!
Leave us alone!
You should stop interfering
in our family affairs.
You promised!
You promised you wouldn't hurt him!
I'm finally going to get some
use out of this awful junk.
Come here.
Look what you did.
Finally something you can be proud of.
- Did you say something?
- I know where the dagger is!
Nothing will stand in our way
now. After capturing the dagger...
- Edgar. stop it!
- Damn it...
Help me!
Let me go!
Where is the dagger?
Where?
Answer!
Find this before they do...
Stop whining. I'm just
giving you what you want.
You liked it when Will hurt
you. Isn't that why you stayed?
Don't pretend to be
deaf. I asked a question.
Susan. help...
Susan. dear.
Can you push the button
and cut this bitch's face off?
It caused chaos in our family.
Your son died because of him.
Do it for Will's sake.
Let me see you!
Oh Susan... Do it!
I'm sorry Alice.
Is this Joseph?
Is this my son?
Come on!
Hurry up!
- What are you doing?!
- Shut your mouth!
Be thankful I didn't leave you there.
Don't you dare move!
Be thankful?
My family is gone.
Everyone I love is gone because of you.
You only caused us pain.
- I hate you.
- Shut up Susan!
Shut up!
I didn't do anything to your
family. They already were..
Do you see this?
Have you seen? Your son did this.
This was the kind of thing he could do.
- It was an accident!
- No it wasn't!
It wasn't.
And you knew it.
You knew it. Susan.
You deserve everything
that happens to you.
Every damn thing.
But you know what?
I've put this behind me now.
I don't give a fuck anymore.
You are right.
Your past is behind you.
Right behind you.
Like a shadow.
There is no escape from this.
Just when you think you're
safe. now that you're healed...
When you breathe a sigh of relief...
My son will be there.
Just like a husband should.
And it will burn you...
Like a whore you are.
You'll be dead before dawn!
Alice!
Help me get up.
I know where the dagger
is. I can help you find him.
Then I'll cut you. just
like my brother should.
You're useless. just
like my grandfather.
Shut your mouth!
He never found it.
You won't find it either.
Let me put an end
to your miserable life.
You already love pain.
That's why you let
Will hurt you. isn't it?
Poor little Alice...
Alone in the attic
They will find you.
From her breasts to
her ass It's so split open.
You didn't want to have
children. So your body is useless.
Wrong knife.
The Circle of Wise Men is dead.
Come here. you little bitch.
I told you he wasn't here.
Listening. correcting. translating into
Turkish and Synchronization; horizonbaba
- My family is leaving...
- Fuck your family!
Did you stay because you liked it?
Or were you too afraid to leave me?
Now look at yourself.
You still can't leave.
Do you remember the
last thing you said to me?
"Go to hell!"
Your wish came true..
I should never have hurt you. Alice.
I should have killed you.
This is where I promise
to always be with you.
Where I promised that even
death couldn't keep us apart.
I'll keep my promise. Alice.
Because without me...
you are nothing.
DANGER
NO LOGIN
Hello?
I could never live without you.
I won't let you live without me either.
Damn...
Where is the dagger?
Where?!
Where is she. Alice?
Go get it yourself.
Listening. correcting. translating into
Turkish and Synchronization; horizonbaba
Where is the dagger?
Sing or burn. bitch!
Here's your damn dagger!
I love you.
This is not enough.
Do you have a cigarette?
- I shouldn't give it away...
- Give me one.
Who did this?
My ex-husband.
EVIL SPIRIT: HELL FIRE
You dirty little French slut!
Ma'am. what happened?
Are you okay?
Thank you darling.
Please help me..
He stole my legs!
But yours are fine.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm